Lowell Thomas Papers: Periodicals
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Thomas led a full and active life into his eighties. Despite the death of Frances in 1975 and the end of his regular news broadcast in 1976, Thomas continued writing drafts of his autobiography with the help of his editor, Lawrence Elliot. Eventually, Thomas wrote a two-part autobiography: “Good Evening Everybody: From Cripple Creek to Samarkand,” published in 1976 and “So Long until Tomorrow: From Quaker Hill to Kathmandu,” published in 1977. Thomas did not retire when he ended his daily news broadcast. He was featured on the television series “Lowell Thomas Remembers” and went on to broadcast hundreds of short radio spots called “The Best Years” about the lives of notable people who accomplished much in their older years. In 1977 Thomas married Marianna Munn. In characteristic style, a 50,000 mile honeymoon to the Arctic, the South Seas and the Himalayas followed their wedding. On 29 August 1981 Lowell Thomas, age 89, died.
This collection consists of various periodicals saved by Lowell Thomas.
Thomas, Lowell, 1892-1981; Thomas, Lowell, 1923-2016; Periodicals; Asia
This collection is organized into 22 series: 1) National Geographic, 2) Geographical Review, 3) The Geographical Journal, 4) The Literary Digest, 5) Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, 6) Asia, 7) Blackwood’s Magazine, 8) Reader’s Digest, 9) Television Daily, 10) Canadian Geographical Journal, 11) American Heritage, 12) Natural History, 13) The New Yorker, 14) Collier’s, 15) The Rinter, 16) Sports Illustrated, 17) Rockefeller Center Weekly, 18) Saks News, 19) Life, 20) Liberty, 21) Book Digest Magazine, and 22) Miscellany.
The collection was donated to Marist College Archives & Special Collections by the Thomas family.
No accruals are expected.
Lowell Thomas Film Collection
Lowell Thomas Memorabilia Collection
Lowell Thomas Papers: Graphic Materials
Lowell Thomas Papers: Objects
Lowell Thomas Papers: Textual Materials
- 1. National Geographic, 1910-1981; 8 boxes
  Series contains issues of National Geographic (formerly The National Geographic Magazine).
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXI Number Eight, August 1910 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXII Number Four, April 1911 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIII Number Two, February 1912 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIII Number Three, March 1912 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIII Number Five, May 1912 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIII Number Eight, August 1912 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIII Number Ten, October 1912 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIV Number Eight, August 1913 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIV Number Ten, October 1913 (Box 1)
  - Possible Section of The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXV Number One, January 1914 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXV Number Two, February 1914 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXV Number Four, April 1914 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine [Volume XXVI Number Six], December 1914 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine [Volume XXVI Number Six], December 1914 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXVII Number Two, February 1915 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXVII Number Three, March 1915 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXVII Number Four, April 1915 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXVIII Number Three, September 1915 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXVIII Number Six, December 1915 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine [Volume XXVIII Number Six], December 1915 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIX Number Three, March 1916 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXIX Number Four, April 1916 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXX Number Three, September 1916 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine [Volume XXXI Number Two], February 1917 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine [Volume XXXII Number One], July 1917 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIII Number One, January 1918 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIII Number Two, February 1918 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIII Number Four, April 1918 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIV Number One, July 1918 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIV Number Two, August 1918 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine [Volume XXXIV Number Three], September 1918 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXV Number One, January 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXV Number Two, February 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXV Number Four, April 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXV Number Five, May 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXV Number Six, June 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVI Number One, July 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVI Number Two, August 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVI Number Five, November 1919 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVII Number One, January 1920 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVII Number Three, March 1920 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVII Number Four, April 1920 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVII Number Six, June 1920 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVIII Number One, July 1920 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVIII Number Two, August 1920 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXVIII Number Four, October 1920 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIX Number Two, February 1921 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIX Number Three, March 1921 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIX Number Three, March 1921 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIX Number Three, March 1921 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XXXIX Number Three, March 1921 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XL Number Three, September 1921 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine [Volume XL Number Five], November 1921 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XLI Number Three, March 1922 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XLI Number Four, April 1922 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XLVI Number One, July 1924 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XLIX Number Three, March 1926 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume L Number Three, September 1926 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume L Number Five, November 1926 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume L Number Six, December 1926 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LI Number One, January 1927 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LI Number Two, February 1927 (Box 1)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LI Number Three, March 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LI Number Four, April 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LI Number Five, May 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LI Number Six, June 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LII Number One, July 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LII Number Two, August 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LII Number Three, September 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LII Number Four, October 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LII Number Five, November 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LII Number Six, December 1927 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIII Number One, January 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIII Number Two, February 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIII Number Three, March 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIII Number Four, April 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIII Number Five, May 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIII Number Six, June 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIII Number Six, June 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIV Number One, July 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIV Number Two, August 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIV Number Three, September 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIV Number Four, October 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIV Number Four, October 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIV Number Five, November 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIV Number Six, December 1928 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LV Number One, January 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LV Number Two, February 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LV Number Three, March 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LV Number Four, April 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LV Number Five, May 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LV Number Six, June 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVI Number Two, August 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVI Number Three, September 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVI Number Four, October 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVI Number Five, November 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVI Number Six, December 1929 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVII Number One, January 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVII Number Two, February 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVII Number Three, March 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVII Number Four, April 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVII Number Five, May 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVII Number Six, June 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVIII Number One, July 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVIII Number Two, August 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVIII Number Three, September 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVIII Number Four, October 1930 (Box 2)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVIII Number Five, November 1930 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LVIII Number Six, December 1930 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIX Number One, January 1931 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIX Number Two, February 1931 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIX Number Three, March 1931 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIX Number Four, April 1931 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIX Number Five, May 1931 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LIX Number Six, June 1931 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LX Number Two, August 1931 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXII Number Four, October 1932 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIV Number Six, December 1933 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIV Number Six, December 1933 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXV Number Four, April 1934 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXV Number Four, April 1934 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXVII Number Two, February 1935 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXVII Number Three, March 1935 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXVIII Number Six, December 1935 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIX Number One, January 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIX Number Two, February 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIX Number Three, March 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIX Number Four, April 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIX Number Five, May 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXIX Number Six, June 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXX Number One, July 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXX Number Two, August 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXX Number Four, October 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXX Number Five, November 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXX Number Six, December 1936 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXI Number Three, March 1937 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXI Number Four, April 1937 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXII Number One, July 1937 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXII Number Six, December 1937 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXV Number One, January 1939 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXV Number Two, February 1939 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXV Number Three, March 1939 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVII Number Three, March 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVII Number Four, April 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVII Number Five, May 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVII Number Six, June 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVIII Number One, July 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVIII Number Two, August 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVIII Number Four, October 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVIII Number Five, November 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXVIII Number Six, December 1940 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXIX Number One, January 1941 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXIX Number Two, February 1941 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXIX Number Three, March 1941 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXIX Number Four, April 1941 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXX Number One, July 1941 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXX Number Two, August 1941 (Box 3)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXX Number Three, September 1941 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXX Number Four, October 1941 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXX Number Five, November 1941 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXX Number Six, December 1941 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXI Number One, January 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXI Number Two, February 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXI Number Three, March 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXI Number Four, April 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXI Number Five, May 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXI Number Six, June 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXII Number One, July 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXII Number Two, August 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXII Number Five, November 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXII Number Six, December 1942 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIII Number One, January 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIII Number Two, February 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIII Number Three, March 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIII Number Four, April 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIII Number Five, May 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIII Number Six, June 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIV Number One, July 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIV Number Two, August 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIV Number Three, September 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIV Number Four, October 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIV Number Five, November 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIV Number Six, December 1943 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXV Number Two, February 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXV Number Three, March 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXV Number Four, April 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXV Number Five, May 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXV Number Six, June 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVI Number One, July 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVI Number Two, August 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVI Number Three, September 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVI Number Four, October 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVI Number Five, November 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVI Number Six, December 1944 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVII Number One, January 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVII Number Two, February 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVII Number Three, March 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVII Number Four, April 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVII Number Five, May 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVII Number Six, June 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVIII Number One, July 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVIII Number Four, October 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVIII Number Five, November 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXVIII Number Six, December 1945 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIX Number One, January 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIX Number Two, February 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIX Number Three, March 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIX Number Four, April 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIX Number Five, May 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume LXXXIX Number Six, June 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XC Number One, July 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XC Number Two, August 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XC Number Three, September 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XC Number Five, November 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XC Number Six, December 1946 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCI Number One, January 1947 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCI Number Two, February 1947 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCI Number Three, March 1947 (Box 4)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCI Number Four, April 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCI Number Five, May 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCI Number Six, June 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCII Number One, July 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCII Number Two, August 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCII Number Three, September 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCII Number Four, October 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCII Number Five, November 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCII Number Five, November 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCII Number Six, December 1947 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCIV Number Six, December 1948 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCVII Number One, January 1950 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume XCIX Number Three, March 1951 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume C Number Five, November 1951 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CI Number Two, February 1952 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CII Number Six, December 1952 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIII Number One, January 1953 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIII Number Three, March 1953 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIII Number Four, April 1953 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIII Number Four, April 1953 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIV Number Four, October 1953 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CVI Number One, July 1954 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CVII Number Six, June 1955 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CVIII Number Four, October 1955 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIX Number One, January 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIX Number Two, February 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIX Number Three, March 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIX Number Four, April 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIX Number Five, May 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIX Number Six, June 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CIX Number Six, June 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CX Number One, July 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CX Number Two, August 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CX Number Three, September 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CX Number Four, October 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CX Number Five, November 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CX Number Six, December 1956 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXI Number One, January 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXI Number Two, February 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXI Number Three, March 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXI Number Three, March 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXI Number Four, April 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXI Number Five, May 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXI Number Six, June 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXII Number Two, August 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXII Number Three, September 1957 (Box 5)
  - The National Geographic Magazine Volume CXII Number Four, October 1957 (Box 5)